<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Answer Dance</title>
    <link>https://answer.dance/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Answer Dance</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://answer.dance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How do I boil eggs?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/how/do/i/boil/eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/how/do/i/boil/eggs/</guid>
      <description> Put eggs in a sauce pan (i.e., a pot) Cover them in water, with at least an inch over them Heat on high and bring the water to a boil Turn off the heat, leave the pot on the burner, and leave them for 10 minutes Pour out the hot water, and run cold water over the eggs  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I take a screenshot on a Mac?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/how/do/i/take/a-screenshot/on/a-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/how/do/i/take/a-screenshot/on/a-mac/</guid>
      <description>The easiest way to take a screenshot on a Mac is to use the keyboard shortcuts.
 To take a screenshot of the entire screen, use option-command-3 (⌥-⌘-3) To take a screenshot of part of the screen, use option-command-4 (⌥-⌘-4). The mouse cursor will change to a crosshairs, which you can drag to select a rectangle you would like to capture.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many beers in a keg?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/how/many/beers/in/a-keg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/how/many/beers/in/a-keg/</guid>
      <description>Kegs come in different sizes.
   Name Gallons Pints 12 oz     1/6 barrel 5.1 40 55   1/4 barrel (pony) 7.75 62 83   European 13.2 105    Half barrel 15.5 124 165    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many cups in a gallon?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/how/many/cups/in/a-gallon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/how/many/cups/in/a-gallon/</guid>
      <description>16</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many feet in a mile?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/how/many/feet/in/a-mile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/how/many/feet/in/a-mile/</guid>
      <description>5280</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many grams in a pound?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/how/many/grams/in/a-pound/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/how/many/grams/in/a-pound/</guid>
      <description>454</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many grams in an ounce?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/how/many/grams/in/an-ounce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/how/many/grams/in/an-ounce/</guid>
      <description>28</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many ounces are in a cup?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/how/many/ounces/in/a-cup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/how/many/ounces/in/a-cup/</guid>
      <description>8</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many ounces in a pound?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/how/many/ounces/in/a-pound/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/how/many/ounces/in/a-pound/</guid>
      <description>16</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many ounces in a quart?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/how/many/ounces/in/a-quart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/how/many/ounces/in/a-quart/</guid>
      <description>32</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How much does the president make?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/how/much/does/the-president/make/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/how/much/does/the-president/make/</guid>
      <description>The US president receives a salary of $400,000 per year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are the countries in the Europen Union?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/are/the-countries/in/the-european-union/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/are/the-countries/in/the-european-union/</guid>
      <description> France Germany Italy Spain Portugal  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are the kinds of clouds?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/are/the-kinds/of/clouds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/are/the-kinds/of/clouds/</guid>
      <description>Clouds are categorized by their height in the atmosphere.
 High  Cirrus clouds are made of ice crystals and look like long, thin, wispy white streamers high in the sky. Cirrocumulus clouds are small rounded puffs that usually appear in long rows high in the sky. Cirrostratus clouds are high, thin sheet-like thin clouds that usually cover the entire sky.   Medium  Altocumulus clouds are mid-level, grayish-white with one part darker than the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are the kinds of diabetes?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/are/the-kinds/of/diabetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/are/the-kinds/of/diabetes/</guid>
      <description>Diabetes is a chronic disease that occurs when the pancreas cannot make insulin, or the body is unable to properly use insulin. There are three kinds of diabetes:
 In Type 1 diabetes, the body produces very little insulin and daily insulin shots are required. In Type 2 diabetes, the body does not make good use of the insulin it produces. Healthy lifestyle can control this kind of diabetes, although insulin may also be needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What does &#34;smh&#34; mean?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/does/smh/mean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/does/smh/mean/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Shaking my head&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What does 69 mean?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/does/69/mean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/does/69/mean/</guid>
      <description>69 is the common name for a sexual position in which two partners perform oral sex on each other simultaneously. It is called 69 because the numerals 6 and 9 together resemble the position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What does a leopard gecko eat?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/does/a-leopard-gecko/eat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/does/a-leopard-gecko/eat/</guid>
      <description>Leopard geckos are insectivores: they eat live insects, such as crickets and mealworms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What does herpes look like?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/does/herpes/look-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/does/herpes/look-like/</guid>
      <description>Herpes is a chronic, viral infection that breaks out from time to time.
Oral herpes appears as sores around the lips or mouth, although they may appear elsewhere on the face.
Genital herpes appear as sores around and in the male and female genitalia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What does poison ivy look like?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/does/poison-ivy/look-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/does/poison-ivy/look-like/</guid>
      <description>Poison ivy has &amp;ldquo;compound&amp;rdquo; leaves, meaning that each leaf is composed of three leaflets. The middle leaflet has a longer stem than the two side leaflets. The stem on the side leaflets can be so small as to be almost invisible, and they are always directly across from each other.
Poison ivy turns yellow or red in the fall. Young vines are smooth, and older vines are hairy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a republic?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/is/a-republic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/is/a-republic/</guid>
      <description>A republic is a form of government in which the country is considered a &amp;ldquo;public matter&amp;rdquo;, rather than being the private concern of a monarch, autocrat, or ruling class who are not accountable to the people. Replublic operate via democracy, or at least with a representative form of government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a server?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/is/a-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/is/a-server/</guid>
      <description>A server is a computer, connected to a network, that other computers connect to in order to perform tasks, access data, or otherwise obtain capabilities that they cannot do themselves. A server is typically located in a different place from the computer that is accessing it: in another room, in a dedicated facility, or even in an unknown location (&amp;ldquo;in the cloud&amp;rdquo;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a Smart TV?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/is/a-smart-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/is/a-smart-tv/</guid>
      <description>A Smart TV is a television that includes hardware and software that enable it to connect to the internet and run applications that obtain and display content, rather than requiring a separate &amp;ldquo;set top box&amp;rdquo; or other interface to deliver content. In addition, Smart TVs may be able to run other applications, and therefore function as a general-purpose home computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a sociopath?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/is/a-sociopath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/is/a-sociopath/</guid>
      <description>A sociopath is a person who does not have empathy for other people, and who is not concerned about how others view them. Sociopaths do not take pleasure in causing harm or pain to others per se, although their lack of regard for others&#39; feelings does lead many sociopaths to engage in behavior that is rewarding or gratifying, but that does injure others. Typical signs include lying, law-breaking, and unsafe behaviors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a thesis (statement)?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/is/a-thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/is/a-thesis/</guid>
      <description>A thesis statement is an important, early element of an essay that clearly communicates the main point or claim that will be made in the essay. It is often, though not always, placed at the end of the first paragraph. The main body of the essay is then dedicated to presenting and discussing examples and evidence in support of the thesis. A good thesis statement is clear, concise, and easy to tell apart from alternative theses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is consequentalism?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/is/consequentalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/is/consequentalism/</guid>
      <description>Consequentialism is a broad family of philosophical thought that places outcomes over intentions. The various forms of consequentialism all maintain that ethical behavior is defined by its actual results, rather than adherence to a set of principles that are viewed as worthy (or honorable) in their own right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is federalism?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/is/federalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/is/federalism/</guid>
      <description>Federalism is a form of government in which power and legal authority are shared between a central government and multiple regional governments. The United States is an example of a federal state, with national and state governments sharing the responsibility and authority of making and enforcing laws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is fracking?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/is/fracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/is/fracking/</guid>
      <description>Fracking is short for &amp;ldquo;hydraulic fracturing&amp;rdquo;. It is a form of natural gas extraction in which large amounts of fluid are injected underground, into rock that contains natural gas. The pressure from the fluid creates small fractures that allow the gas to release and be reclaimed on the surface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Good Friday?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/is/good-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/is/good-friday/</guid>
      <description>In Christianity, Good Friday is a holiday commemmorating the crucifixion of Jesus Christ. It is celebrated on the Friday preceding East Sunday, and it is observed with worship services and prayer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is human resources?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/is/human-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/is/human-resources/</guid>
      <description>Human resources (HR) is a department or function within a company that is responsible for &amp;ldquo;hiring and firing&amp;rdquo; employees. The hiring function includes recruiting, salary and job negotiation. After employees are hired, HR is responsible for monitoring and enforcing codes of behavior, both those specific to the company and those required for compliance to regulation. When an employee will be terminated, either with or without cause, and as an individual or as part of a group, HR is typically the department most involved in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Parler?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/is/parler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/is/parler/</guid>
      <description>Parler is a microblogging site, similar in many ways to Twitter, that became popular among right-wing and conservative users when Twitter began to more strongly enforce content and community standards, a process which lead to the removal of content that violated those terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is socialism?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/is/socialism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/is/socialism/</guid>
      <description>Socialism is a form of government in which resources are distributed evenly among the citizens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is the currency of the United States?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/is/the-currency/of/the-united-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/is/the-currency/of/the-united-states/</guid>
      <description>The US Dollar, abbreviated USD</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is WAP?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/what/is/wap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/what/is/wap/</guid>
      <description>WAP stands for &amp;ldquo;Wet Ass Pussy&amp;rdquo;. It is the name of a hit song from 2020, a collboration between Cardi B and Megan Thee Stallion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When did women get the right to vote?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/when/did/women/get/the-right/to/vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/when/did/women/get/the-right/to/vote/</guid>
      <description>In the United States, women gained the right to vote with the passage of the 19th amendment to the Constitution in 1920. Before its passage, many individual states had passed laws granting women the right to vote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When is Mothers&#39; Day?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/when/is/mothers-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/when/is/mothers-day/</guid>
      <description>In the United States, Mothers&#39; Day is the second Sunday in May.
   Year Date     2020 May 10   2021 May 9   2022 May 8   2023 May 14   2024 May 12    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When was the internet invented?</title>
      <link>https://answer.dance/when/was/the-internet/invented/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://answer.dance/when/was/the-internet/invented/</guid>
      <description>The internet is a combination of multiple technologies, which were developed over decades at US universities and government research labs. Arguably the most central of these to the internet, the Transmission Control Protocol and Internet Protocol (TCP/IP) were published in 1974. The first demonstration connecting multiple networks took place in 1977.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
